Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Government business and correspondence, 1982-1990; Series 2
  - Correspondence and official business of government branches of the United States and DC governments, 1985-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Forman, James, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Fiscal Year 1987 Budget Revision, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Fiscal Year 1989 Budget, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Furlough of DC Government Employees, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Fred Rader U.S. Senate Florida, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - The Georgia General Assembly, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Home Rule, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - House Committee on the District of Columbia, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - House of Representatives Committee of the District of Columbia Summary Report, 1985-1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Housing and Environmental Regulation Administration, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Independent Boards and Commissions, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Innaugural 1987-1989, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Intergovernment Liaison Office, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Judicial Nominations Commissions, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Koch, Edward (NYC Mayor), 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Mayor's Office on Latino Affairs, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Mayor Marion Barry 1987, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Mayor's Orders, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Mayor's Urban Fellows Program, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Mayor's Youth Leadership Institute, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Mayor's Youth Leadership Institution Roster, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Mayoral Condidates - Tours, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Gerald, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Labor Camp Agreements [1/2], 1985-1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Labor Camp Agreement [2/2], 1985-1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Loitering Task Force, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Maps & Atlas, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Marion Barry's Blue Ribbon Commission, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Marion Barry - Correspondence, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Mayor - Correspondence, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Mayor's Advisory Committee on Executive Pay, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Mayor's Commission on Food, Nutrition and Health, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Mayor's Commission on Handicapped Individuals, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Mayor's Committee on Handicapped Individuals, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Washington Council of Gov., 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Washington Crusade, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Mini-Commission on Aging Swearing In, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Ministers to Consider For Meeting With Mayor Barry, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Minority Business Opportunity Commission [1/2], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Minority Business Opportunity Commission [2/2], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Minority Business Opportunity Commission, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Monthly Reprogramming Reports, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - National Capital Planning Commission, 1987-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - National Conference of Black Mayors, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - National Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - National Conference of State Legislators [1/2], 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - National Conference of State Legislators [2/2], 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - National Conference on State Legislatures, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - National Highway Traffic Dafety Administration, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - National Park Service, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - News Releases, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Notice of Final Rulemaking, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Notices of Public Hearing, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - November Election 1988, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Advisory Board, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Office of the General Counsel- Council of DC, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - OM Extradition, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Otis Troupe, DC Auditor, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - People's Counsel for the District of Columbia - Crawford, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Personal Care Aide Program, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Prison Task Force, 1988-1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Public Hearing on Consumer Utility Board, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Public Housing Advisory Board, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Public Service Award, Annual D.C. Employee, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Public Service Commission, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Public Service Commission of the District of Columbia, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Public Works Committee, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The Proposed 1987 Supplemental District Budget, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Reagan, Nancy, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Referral of Reprogramming Request, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Relocation of the Mental Health, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Rent Control Officials, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Rental Housing Commission, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Residency Policy, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - residency Requirments for DC Employees, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Senator Jesse Helms, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Frank, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Russell, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Statehood, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Statehood Lobbying [1/3], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Statehood Lobbying [2/3], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Statehood Lobbying [3/3], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - State Issues Forum, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - State Legislative Leaders Foundation, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Subcommittee on Aviation, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Summer Youth Employment Program, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Memorial Bridge, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Timmer, John, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Transportation Management Program Work Shop for Federal Agencies, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - United States District Court for the District of Columbia, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - United States Department of Transportations, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - US Environmental Protection Agency, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - US House of representatives, 1987-1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - US House of Representatives, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - United States Senate, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Ward #8, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Washington Airports Task Force, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Washington Convention Center, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Wilson Amendment - Home Rule, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Women's Program, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - World Congress of Local Government for a Sustainable Future, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - YEA Participates, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Youth Employment Program, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Youth Employment Program - Does General Information, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Youth Employment Services Out of School Program, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Government Business and Correspondence, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Government Business and Correpondence, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Personal and office files, 1985-1990; Series 3
  This series contains employee files resumes, resignations, forms, reading files, leave requests, personal travel and expenses, office procedures, news releases, memos, press releases, and condolences and congratulations. This material dates from 1985-1990.
  - Administrative Issuance System, 1988; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Anacostia Gateway - Mailing List, 1985; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Applications, Undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Arnold, Eddie T., 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta Georgia November 24-27, 1989, 1990; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Barnes, Debbie, Undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Beijing Trip, 1988; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Bernstein, Betty, 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Bob Bethea, 1988; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Booker, Melody R. 299-64-4646, 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Briscoe, Joseph, 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Butler-Turner, Catharyn A., 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Danile Butler - Resume, Undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Churches - Mailing List, Undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Condolences, 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Congratulations, Undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1989; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Contributions Requests, 1990; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1987; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence [1/2], 1987; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence [2/2], 1988; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Dashiell, Martha, Undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Directory of Certified Minority Business Enterprisie (list), 1986; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Cox, Terri, 1990; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Employed Applications, 1984; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Employee Files - A, 1989; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Employee Files - B, 1985-1989; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Employee Files - C [1/2], 1983-1989; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Employee Files - C [2/2], 1983-1989; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Employee Files - D, 1983-1989; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Employee Files - E, 1985; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Employee Files - K, 1985; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Employee Files - L, 1985-1988; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Eng, Ronald, 1983-1985; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Factors for Preformance Rating, Undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Flyers/News Letters, 1986-1987; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Fort Stanton Civic Association Senior Citizen Park Guest List, 1985; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Foxworth, Rhonda, 1989; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Frazier, Victoria, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Fuller, Gail, 1987; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising, 1987; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising List, 1987; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Funeral Directors (Mailing List), Undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - General Office Procedures, 1990; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - General Office Workers, 1984; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Goodwin, Mary, 1986; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Teri Gross, 1987; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Teri Gross Lawsuit [1/2], 1988; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Teri Gross Lawsuit [2/2], 1988; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Harper, Lasandra M., 1988; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Hart Levine, Jody, 1988; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Henderson, Carmelita, 1987; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Hill, Walter, 1987; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Hines, Caryn, 1989; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Hinton, Marcieta, 1985-1986; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hirsh, June, 1990; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Holmes, Michael, 1989; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Hunter, Carolyn E., 1989; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Hutta, Jane, 1990; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - In School Program Signature Sheets, Print out Sheet, 1989; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Inter Office Correspondence, 1983-1989; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Inter-Office Memos, 1988; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Invitations Accepted, 1989; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Invitations Regretted, 1989; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - January 1990, Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - John R. Jackson, 1990; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Benjamin, 1987; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Jennifer, Undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Wanda, 1987; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Johnsonville, S.C. September 7, 1989, Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Deborah, 1985; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Eric, 1987; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Keisha L., 1985; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Jones, Steven, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Kaplan, Richard, 1985; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Kersey, Lovetta, 1985; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - King, Sandra, 1990; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Lawsuits, 1990; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Lease, Undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Leave Records, 1989; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Leave Requests, 1983-1985; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Lee, Nathea, 1990; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Letters of Support, 1984; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Lillion, Lenny, 1989; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Lockett, Gretchen, Undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Lorraine County Project August 18-20, 1989, Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Maier, Adam, 1990; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Mailing Lists, 1988; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Mailing Register, Undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Mallard, Stephanie, 1989; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Malloy, Linda, 1985; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Market Kow Businesses - Mailing List, Undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Marshall, Sheila, 1986-1987; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Cherie Renee McClam, Volunteer, Undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Margaret Q. McKee, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Memorandums, 1984-1985; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Alice, 1986; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Miller, Joyce A., 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Moody, Fredreatha, 1987; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Moses, Elizabeth Ann, 1987; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Nadine Winter Info, 1988; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Nellis AFB Attendees, 1985; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - New York, New York, August 23-26, 1989, Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Notes, Undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, 1986; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - News Release, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - News Release: Council Majority to Rule Greyhound Bus Strike Protestors, March 22, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - News Release: Winter Clears Air on Parking Fine Increases, April 3, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - News Release: Winter Moves Ahead With Tax Avoidance Package, March 8, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - News Release: Winter Plans Spring Clean Up, March 28, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - News Release: Winter Pours Cold Water On Barry Resignation, Special Election Gossip, January 23, 1990; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - News Release: Winter Sourson District Recycling Efforts..., November 15, 1989; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - NPW Travel - General, 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Oathe of Office, Undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Ocean City Maryland Trip, July 21, 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Office Procedures, 1987; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Jimmie Owens, 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Parker, Teresa, 1986; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Patricia Hester, 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Personal, 1987; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Personal, 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Policy & Procedure File, 1987; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Phillips, Vaughn, 1990; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Pictures, Undated; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Pamela Pope, 1988-1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Press Conferences, 1988-1990; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Press Information Tour, 1988; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Price, Shirley Ann, 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Questine, Harvey, 1985-1986; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Ray, Kimberly, 1985; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Reading File, April 1989; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Reading File - April 1989 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Reading File May 1989 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Reading File May 1989 [2/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Reading File - June 1989 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Reading File - June 1989 [2/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Reading File - July 1989 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - July 1989 [2/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Reading File August 1989 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Reading File August 1989, Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Reading File September 1989, Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Reading File - June 1990 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Reading File - June 1990 [2/2], Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Receipts, 1983-1985; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1988-1989; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Regrets, 1986; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Requisition for Services, Supplies and Equipment, 1989; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Resignation, 1989; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Resume, 1987; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Resumes: A.A. Position, 1984; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Reynolds, Patricia, 1987; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Rich, Renee, 1988; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Richardson, Alice, 1983; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Roberts, Matthew, 1988-1989; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Reading File December 1989, Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Reading File - April 1990 [1/2], Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Reading File April 1990 [2/2], Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Shelton, Melanie, 1986; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Slaughter, Robert, 1987; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Sharon, 1988; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Yvonne, 1986-1987; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, 1988-1989; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Reginald Spriggs, 1989; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Marcia Y. Sandford-Martin, 1990; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Sands, Cheryl E., 1990; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Sharon Smith, Undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Slaughter, Robert L., 1989; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Slye, Robin, 1989; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Staff Leave Calendar, Undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Statement Before the Press, 1985; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Strother, Lisa, 1988; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Summer Job (Youth), 1989; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Support Letters, 1986-1989; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Thank You Letters, 1989-1990; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Time and Attendance Records, 1983; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Rolfstad, John, 1987; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Routing File Forms, Undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Sacramento, California October 4-6, 1989, Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Salazar, Thomas, 1987; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Time Sheets, Undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Travel 89, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Travel Expenses, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Travel Expenses Form, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Tulsa, Oklahoma Convention August 6, 1989, Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Urban Homestead - Mailing List, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Walker, David, 1985-1987; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Waller, Charlene Denise, 1986; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Waller, Tanya, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - War on Rats, 1982; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Washington, Adria, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Washington DC March 11, 1989, Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Washington DC Press Conference, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Watts, Cassandra, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Webb, Raychiel, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Weekend Schedule, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - West, Shelia D., 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Wiggins, Lillian, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Williams, LaShawn, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Winter, Nadine P., 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Winter, Nadine, 1983; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - NPW's Europe Trip (W. Germany - Switzerland), 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Working With You: Winter Blossoms Into Spring may 10, 1990, Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Wright, Carlton, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Yates, Rev. Harold, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Youth Employment Program, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Personal and Office Files [1/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Personal and Office [2/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Personal and Office Files [1/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Personal and Office Files [2/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Personal and Office Files [1/2], 1989; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Personal and Office Files [2/2], 1989; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Personal and Office Files [1/2], 1989; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Personal and Office Files [2/2], 1989; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Personal and Office Files [1/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Personal and Office Files [2/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 6)